Greetings, Sir Trillram. My landing castle is about to go dark, so this transmission will be terminated soon.
So let's wrap this up quickly. Have you taken care of our little rat problem?
Are you awake?
Oh, no you don't. We need to keep you here in bed.
Where am I?
We're at the school for now. The Martians haven't figured out that we're here yet. We've stayed out of sight pretty well so far.
And what about the others?
You mean Inaho and his friends?
They say they're going to fight.
Using the equipment here.
Against the Martian cataphract.
Without the clock.
I Weihnfaced.
You shouldn't.
Oh
What the hell's going on here
Orders from headquarters, sir
We will be abandoning this base as soon as all the remaining citizens have been evacuated
We've still got an active unit out in combat
You're this area's only surviving fighter
Lieutenant Koichiro Marito
And you would be?
Darzana Mogberech
With the 4th Fleet Escort Force
CO Watatsumi Amphib Assault Ship
This is my XO, Kaoru Mizusaki
One of our people is still out there fighting
The only reason we're still secure here is because she's holding them off
Who is she?
Warrant officer Yuki Kaisuka
An EM field is damping radio signals around Shinowara
GPS is down too
Even if we tried to rescue her, we don't know her location
But Captain Chi
Our orders are to escort and protect refugees evacuating by ferry
But there are still people who haven't made it out yet
I didn't see my kids' names in the passenger manifest
They're my students
All right then
I'll submit a request to put together a rescue party for you
I can only leave you a single landing craft
However, if you can't assemble enough people to be her crew
Then you'll have to just forget about it
I'm sorry
Now! You're in there still, right?
Answer me! Now!
Occupied
I know that! That's why I'm knocking!
Do you have the slightest idea what you're all getting yourselves into?
I'm perfectly aware that it seems insane
Then why are you doing it?
We don't know why
But that Martian seems quite obsessed with trying to kill us
But as long as we're at the school
His attacks won't hit the harbor or the city either
Luckily, they evacuated everyone who lives around here
That doesn't mean you
And he killed Okisuke
Be more flexible
Look at things and make the call
Go with your gut
Isn't that what you always tell me, Yuki?
I think that it applies most right now
Then let me take care of it
You can't do it injured, Yuki
You're so stubborn
Everyone is affected by this
That's why I want you to be the one to comfort them
You can be here to cheer up the sad
And to reassure the frightened
After all, we students aren't capable of it
Princess
You desired peace more than anyone
Who would do this?
So you are saying that not only did you fail to kill the rat
You've lost track of where she's gone to ground?
With great respect, my lord Sosbaum
This elusive rat has only managed to delay the inevitable
And?
The tunnel used for escape only leads to one area
Shinawara's northernmost district
When she impatiently pokes her little head up for a look
My Nilo Keras' eagle eyes will immediately spot her
You are a fool
Do you think we have the luxury of playing a waiting game?
If we do not have the rat's exact location
We shall simply turn the entire city to dust
We'll use meteors to bombard them
But, my lord Sosbaum
Count Cruteo's landing castle may be positioned too close for that
He may have the impression that he is being attacked
Collateral damages
Orbital corrections will take several hours
To ensure the rat does not flee elsewhere in the meantime
Maintain a close watch
Yes, my lord
What's that?
It's the Mars cataphract data I've collected
It's very interesting
The bullets you fired at it didn't bounce off
They were all absorbed, weren't they?
How's the signal for you?
Not that great
The impudence
And now
It's not just ammunition
Sensor pings hit it
But there are no return signals
And that means what?
Infrared, acoustical, lasers
They're all useless
Not so much as an echo comes back
It seems to be absorbing everything
From radio waves to even kinetic energy
That is the key part
The wall's special characteristic
The wall?
The cataphract's energy field covering its entire surface
You could call it a barrier, I guess
A barrier?
Yeah
A barrier that absorbs anything coming at it
Matter, sound, EMF, all of it
But then
If that's the case, how can he still see us?
Through the barrier, nothing should be visible to him
Huh?
All information from the outside is blocked by the barrier
Therefore, it's logical to assume he can't actually see or hear anything on this side of it
The data we've gathered so far says that the inside
Appears to be completely black
Wait, so then how does he target us so accurately?
Yeah, you're right
How can he hit anything if he wasn't even able to see it?
You remember?
He was able to target us precisely from the other side of a building
But then
Though he was almost right on top of us
He gave up the chase the instant we went into the tunnel
I would bet
He wasn't the one that was watching everything around him
I think that he's using another camera system
To feed him the visuals
Most likely some kind of high-level drone
Kind of like this
And so that was how he was able to stay on us no matter where we ran
And why he didn't follow us in the tunnel
He can't see anything for himself when that barrier is up
He's probably searching for us right now from overhead
That makes sense
And that means we'll be safe just as long as we stay undercover like we are now
Yes, but the moment we go out again, he'll spot us
We'll probably only get one chance at this
Oh no, don't tell me that we're out of backup batteries
Well, whose turn was it to check him this week?
Marito, of course
So, Inaho
It's gonna be three of us heading out in the Cats
So we need two more people for the decoy truck then, right?
So who do we ask?
Excuse me
Is there some way that I may help?
No, don't
That European, babe
I feel it is my duty to do anything possible to assist in this time of crisis
A bit dramatic
Let me help
I watched him kill my father
Let me take part in this too
Our lives will be on the line
I understand
You can count on me
We carry out the plan tomorrow morning
We leave at first light
We're going to get rid of that Martian cataphract
You still working?
Huh?
Are you having trouble sleeping too, Inko?
The conference room is pretty cold
Yeah, we turned the heat off in there
We're trying to minimize any evidence that we're here
Yeah, well, Kam is sleeping like a baby
Hope he doesn't catch cold
What is it?
It seems funny that you're worried about a cold
Especially when all of us might die tomorrow
I'm sorry
It's okay
I mean, it's not like I'm fearless or anything
I thought I was going to be able to save him
But then he was just gone
So suddenly
If that happens to us
There probably won't be time to prepare ourselves
Who knows what regrets we'll have at that moment
I can't bear to just sit around doing nothing as I think about that
I have to keep going
That's how I feel
Kam probably does too
If you're not up for this, Inko
Oh, no, I'm fine
I'll go rest up for tomorrow
Inaho
Remember, don't catch cold
You too, Inko
First, let me thank you all
We five will carry out the mission to rescue friendly forces and civilians
Who are still in Shinawara's northern district
You can make that we six
Captain Mogberech?
I've delegated ferry escort duties to my XO
We'll meet them again when the operation is complete
Let's move out
I am quite interested in you
Lieutenant Koichiro Marito
What are those things over there?
They're signals
Three reds
That's over by the school
That means commencing attack
All right, we're moving out
Oh, my little rat
Let's finish this
All right, we're moving out
Everyone, follow me
This road's really narrow
Don't worry
She won't get any points deducted today
There it is
Ten o'clock
Got you now, stink bug
Commence operation
Right
You little rodents
Not again
Look, he stopped moving
Like he not host anyone
Good
Hey, you gotta flip off the safety
Then point
And fire
Simple, right?
Mm-hmm
You stinking little earth rats!
Kaisuka, you all right?
Lieutenant Marito!
Sir Turan, what's going on?
What the hell?
That was not in the plan
Pinpoint that vehicle
Huh?
Give me its position
Tell me where it is!
It's southwest of you
Toward the center of the city
That guy's out of control
Cover me
The weight from that plane
Is clearing our smoke away
We gotta shoot it down
Wait, calm!
They're using cataphracts against us
Right now
But it's all
Back on the floor
Ah!
Sorry for this
Mom!
Oh no!
You okay?
Yeah!
Stabilizer's gone
But I can still run
Barely
Rockets seem to work on that one
Skycarrier
It's a burst tactical transport
It doesn't really have any special equipment
Just standard machine guns and rocket missiles
Begin smoke screen
Right
Checking all systems
Voltage check
Oil pressure check
RPM's at normal
Force feedback checking program
Start
Ejection seat functional
IFF online
Tactical data link
Activated
It's coming
All systems green
Hold open
They're in my sights
1200 meters to location
Our estimated arrival
Is in 93 seconds
I'll buy some time
Just be quiet for a minute
You dare to mock me like that?
Oh, that was a lovely chase
Get out and run
It's me that he's after
I will not
It's 54 seconds to our rendezvous point
From here, I take over
How pathetic
So you're begging for your lives?
Stop this!
These outrageous actions
Must now end
In the name of the royal princess of verse
Her highness of Salem versus Lucia
It can't be
Stand down
I command it
Impossible
That's not possible
All missiles fire
We need to take out that Martian cataphract
Wait, how can you be alive?
Okay now
Master arm switch enabled
Fire control is on
Lower the dampers
Ingo, hurry!
All right!
You fools
Mighty Locaris is invulnerable
You can't even scratch it
Correcting aim
Zero six
Zero two
Fire!
Fire, fire, fire, fire!
Look, the water is
Damn you!
Talk to me
Hold on
The soles of its feet
Anything else?
Inaho, found it
The water's not going in
To the right of the intake
Between the claws
The rear armor
It can't be
We knew that your barrier
Had to have a gap in it somewhere
Under your feet for instance
You couldn't have a barrier there
Otherwise, you wouldn't be able
To stand on the ground
The very nature of your barrier
Means you can't cover yourself
In it completely
The receiver for your flying cameras
There's another barrier gap
This is for my friend
Were they able to get him?
To the health of the要素
Yes!
boi
Woo
Can't be
Whoa
That's interesting
The princess of mars
Hey,
始まりにも
終わりにも
変わる光
下に
向けたまま
かざすの
やめた
あの時
NPの
サイズの合わない
嘘ばかり
並べて
見失い
自ら
全てに
つまついた
明日
照らす
8A
繰り返す
Found
明日の
0時の
Sign
雷暮大
見えない
光の線
持ちだけで
生きる場所捨てて
名前の
いない
そこに
答えを
戻れてても
風に
溶かした
命の霊
投げ捨てない
駆け出しの
涙
災いも
闇も
ありも
いらない
ゼロに
なれば
あたしも
合う
チェイル
出入し
トレーナ
But wait, my lord! Princess Asalem! She's alive! I don't understand.
I know she is! That's why I'm going to kill her and make certain of it this time!
What kind of an idiot are you, Terran?
If we let her stay alive, my entire clan will surely be branded as traitors!
Now let's go.
Oh, really? What are you doing, scum?
Give that to me!
In the parade, you were the ones who tried to assassinate the princess!
Yes! You will regret this!